- So "tenured" means ajob for life?
- Yep.
And you can't get fired...
(Penny:)...even if you're bad at it?
- Mm, not really.
(Penny:)Wow, sounds a lot like being a pretty
waitress at the Cheesecake Factory.
(Sheldon:)While I disagree
with the premise of tenure...
(Sheldon:)...if they gave it to me,
it wouldn't diminish my output.
I'm like the sun. I can't turn this off.
- Are Rajesh and Leonard competing as well?
- Mm-hm.
(Amy:)Do they know they don't stand a chance
because you're so great?
(Sheldon:)Well put.
(Sheldon:)I must say, I go back and forth
on this boyfriend-girlfriend thing...
(Sheldon:)...but those moments when you worship me
really keep you in the running.
It would be nice to have the income,
stop taking money from my parents.
(Howard:)Money from family does come
with strings attached.
(Raj:)You have no idea.
(Raj:)They buy me a new BMW for my birthday,
but can I get seat warmers? No.